[metal clashing]
The Tiny Loser Chamber needs to be fixed!
Help me get it fixed!
Please! Be quiet, and leave me alone!
Hup!
- It's a message!
- What's it say?
"We are currently building an
Announcer Recovery Center...
It will be done soon."
Signed, Flykydfly.
Well that's good. I miss the old Announcer.
I can't wait to have him back!
- Wow!
- Ice Cube!
You're supposed to be in the TLC.
How did you escape?
T-there's a giant gaping hog hole in the wall, so...
- Coiny: Wow, thanks for stating the obvious.
- Firey: Huh! What? What's that?
Oh, hello, Coiny! It's good to see that
you're finally where you belong.
[rapid slapping]
[INTRO PLAYS]
Subtitles: TAFFYMARZI
See? I told you the TLC needed to be fixed!
Yeah, that's true. But how are you gonna fix it?
Well, I just need some more metal to fix it and...
you guys are... metal, uhm, so... yeah...
I don't want to go first!
Bubble, you go first!
Ahhh!-
Who's next? Who's next?
Leafy, who should go next?
Hmm... Aha! Ice Cube, come on down,
you can be in my alloy!
Ahhhh!
Uh, why would you do that?
- She isn't even made of metal.
- Firey, don't question it.
- Just jump in!
- Ahhhh!
Who's next, Leafy?
- How about you?
- What?! No!
You have to go in eventually!
Well, I can't go in now. I-
Leafy, Spongy, and Flower:
Ahhhh!
Yes! Now I finally have enough.
Yes, I'm no longer metal! I don't weigh
like a thousand pounds anymore!
Whoa! The Tiny Loser Chamber... it's been fixed!
One of you will be sent to the TLC in about one minute
and one of you will be sent to the TLC in 5 seconds.
Sorry Ice Cube, I guess you have to go back.
- Wha?
- [whisper] Sorry...
Now, let's do Cake at Stake.
♪ The points are gone ♪
♪ We are free of them now ♪
♪ But we look on ♪
♪ To the moment that we see ♪
♪ The next slice of cake ♪
♪ A step closer to the prize ♪
♪ Brought on by Cake at Stake ♪
Hey guys, I'm back.
Who's this? An impostor?
No, no, no, I'm your replacement.
- And I'm his clone.
- Say what?
Both:
We are also clones!
You people are all too weird.
- Please leave.
- No discrimination, please.
I am the circular floating globe.
And I'm the Cheese Orb!
I throw spike balls uncontrollably!
Hey, um, let's just get to the elimination.
Yeah, let's... let's do that.
Bwahhh!
816 voters voted. It went down again.
Please don't cry!
Don't worry. I'm okay.
But if it goes down for a third time in a row,
I swear I'll cancel BFDI.
Would you please stop distracting me?
So, what's the cake this time?
- It's cheesecake.
- But we don't have any-
Now we do.
Oh no! Speaker just killed the Cheese Orb!
Cheese Orb was my friend!
Four of the five of you are safe, and will get cake.
One of you will be eliminated.
Flower and Firey had immunity, so they get cake.
With only 97 votes against her, Bubble is safe.
Spongy and Leafy, one of you will be eliminated.
- Leafy: Bmbmbmbmbmbmbmbmbmb!
- Spongy: Wha?!
The contestant who is safe with only 287 votes is-
- It's Leafy.
- Oh my gosh, would you just be quiet?
But is it true?
- Yes. Spongy...
- Huh?
...with a record of 432 votes,
you've been eliminated, again.
Yeah, final four, Firey!
Do you realize that there is only one
more elimination before the finals?
Woah!
That means that this is the last contest of BFDI.
And what is the last contest?
Announcer:
It's a combination of all the previous contests.
Ooh, cool!
The first person to complete all the
contests in order wins immunity.
If you die, you have to start all over again. Go.
Out of my way, I need my space!
Firey:
Ahhhh!
Haha!
Huh?
Huh, I deserve the one with the motor!
Hup!
Ohh...
Faster!
Well I never did this contest! This is unfair!
Huh?
Firey, I'll wait for you!
Bubble, get me to the top of the rock wall!
No, Flower, you have to do it yourself.
What? And to think you're nice!
Firey! You can have the larger boat,
because I know you can't touch water.
Wow, thanks!
Bubble, y-you have to get me to the top!
- You have to!
- No!
If you don't help me, I'll... I'll pop you!
- You wouldn't!
- Oh yeah?!
Huh?!
Ahhhh!
Oh, why, hello!
Oh no, no boats left!
It's okay, we can swim!
Oh, okay!
Hey! It's my boat! I must have let go of it earlier.
So, um...
You can use it, Bubble!
Really? Thanks!
Firey, you'll get me to the top!
- No!
- I'll extinguish you!
- No, you won't!
- Oh yeah?!
Firey:
Huh?!
Euugh!
Firey's about to fall into the water!
Huu-EUUUGH!
I'll save you!
- Huu-Ahhhh!
- Yes! Ow, hot!
Ahhhhh!
Bubble, now it's just the two of us.
Now get me to the top!
I am only doing this because
you'll kill me if I don't!
Yes! Three, two, one!
- Guh!
- Wheee!
Ahhhhh!
Oh no, all the boats are gone,
and you know I can't swim.
I'll swim, Firey, and you can stand on my head!
Really?
As long as you don't set me on fire!
Wow, thanks!
- Firey: This is great!
- Flower: Ahhhhh!
- Leafy: Huh?
Flower:
Ahhhhh!
No, don't die!
♪ Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo! ♪
Yoylecake!
Done!
Oh no!
[Firey pants] Hup!
Ha-ha!
Oh no!
Done!
Yay!
Yes!
Oh noio!
Hup! Hey, Bubble, what happened?
I failed the test three times!
I think I can help you!
Really?
Yeah! All you have to know for the test is
that you can survive 1338 days without eating,
and that you like tennis balls!
- That's it?
- Yeah!
So, we have to make a cake.
Well, I remember Coiny made a
delicious dirt cake, so I'm getting that, too.
But Coiny's so dumb! Don't follow his ways!
Whatever, I'm moving on.
Guh! Ahhhhh!
Yoy-le-cake!
Yay!
Firey, why are you actually baking a cake?
A clump of dirt would work just as well.
Yeah, I think I'll do that too!
Firey:
OMG, what has Coiny done to you?!
Leafy and Bubble:
Hup! Hup! Hup!
Waaaaaah!
Oh, no. This is a maroon ball!
Hup! Hup! Hup! Hup!
Hup!
So, all I have to do is escape,
and I've got immunity into the final 3!
- That's right!
- Woah!
How did you guys catch up so quickly?
Psh, well it was pretty easy.
And now I'm going to win immunity!
No, you're not, Flower!
Oh no!
Ahh!
Huh? Wait, what does 'Delete Pole' mean?
Good thing I can survive in lava.
But not water, can you?! Ha-ha!
Ahhhhh!
Well, it's going to be a long time before
Firey and Flower get here again.
So I guess it's just the two of us!
- I think you should win the immunity, Bubble!
- Uhm,
Leafy, no offense, but I'm tired of
you being so nice all the time.
What?!
It's not much fun when I know you'll
probably let me win anyway.
There's no challenge!
You mean all this time, I've been trying to
help you and you're not even thankful?
- Well, I didn't mean to say that!
- I was right about you.
You are the meanest person on EARTH!
No, I am thankful, it's just-
I bet you'd rather be with Flower, wouldn't you?
Yeah! She would!
See? I knew it.
No, Leafy, I-
Bubble even helped me over the rock wall!
You WHAT?!
No, that's only because
she threatened me to-
I don't wanna hear it, Bubble!
Our friendship is over!
Well ours, Bubble, has just begun!
Now get me out of this volcano!
Three, two, one-
Wait! What are you doing?
Ahhhh!
Bubble, you win the final immunity ticket.
So Firey, Flower and Leafy are
up for the final elimination.
- Firey?
- Yeah?
For dying the most in this episode, you get a penalty.
What? Ugh, what is it?
Announcer:
You have to hold this sign.
Uhm... This doesn't seem too bad.
Voters, viewers and everyone, vote who you
think should be eliminated by commenting on this video.
Hey wait, so if there's an
Announcer Recovery Center now,
we can kill the Announcer as much as we want.
He'll still come back to give us Dream Island!
Oh yeah! Hmmm...